http://www.willmsshier.com/our-firm/privacy-policy

Community Training and Capacity Building
Corporate Development, Economic Development & Strategic Planning
Environmental Risk Analysis or Risk Assessment
Environmental Site Assessment (ESA) (Federal and Provincial)
First Nations & Environmental Law
Government Policy & Law
Green Intellectual Property Protection
Land Use Planning & Development
Municipalities (Environmental Law for Municipalities)
John
J. P.
Privacy Policy
AccomplishmentsCLE SeminarsCareer OpportunitiesCasesMembershipsTestimonials
Willms & Shier is committed to respecting and protecting your privacy and personal information.
Willms & Shier does not use cookies nor does Willms & Shier use any electronic means to automatically collect personal information from you or your computer; however, Willms & Shier web servers will automatically collect IP addresses and we may view our web server IP log from time to time to prevent fraudulent acts and possible network attacks.
The only personal information Willms & Shier collects via the Website is the information voluntarily supplied by you when you register for access or subscribe to our publications.
It is the policy Willms & Shier to treat your personal information as private and confidential and to restrict the use and disclosure of such personal information to the specific purpose for which it was provided. Willms & Shier will not sell your personal information to any third party unless specifically authorized by you to do so or as required by law. We may use your name and address/email address to send you information on environmental law, or promoting our services, or related services that we believe may interest you.
Although we strive to ensure that your personal information is protected at all times, we cannot guarantee that your communication over the Internet is fully secure or that the information you transmit to Willms & Shier will not be intercepted and/or misused by third parties.
At all times, you shall have the right to access, verify and amend your personal information provided to and maintained by Willms & Shier. In addition, you also have the right to withdraw your consent to the collection and treatment of your personal information by Willms & Shier. To access, edit or delete your personal information provided to Willms & Shier, please contact info@www.willmsshier.com . Willms & Shier reserves the right to maintain your personal information off-line as may be required or permitted by applicable law.
In providing Willms & Shier with personal information through the Website, you consent to the collection and treatment of that information in accordance with this privacy policy.
Revised: Oct 04, 2005
